Contact

Address:

Abuja, Nigeria

Phone:

+234-902-772-7023

Email:

Sidiali0203@gmail.com

Hobbies

- Travelling
- Sight-seeing
- Listening to music
- Writing

Application Proficiency

Microsoft Office

Adobe Photoshop

Canva

Adobe Premiere

Pro

Corel Draw

ABDUL-LATEEF SIDI-ALI

Summary

Dedicated, focused and result-oriented administrative personnel with experience in planning and managing of appointments and communications. Possess a BSc in Mass communication with demonstrated community building prowess.

Skills

Excellent Communication, Problem Resolution, Influential Team player, Creative Thinking, Conversion of ideas to design, Brand strategy, Design thinking, Copywriting.

Work Experience

RETIREMENT BENEFITS ADVISORY (Abuja, Nigeria)

JAN 2021 - DATE

Executive Consultant Trainee

- Responsible for creating designs and social media templates for the firm using design apps such as Canva and Adobe Photoshop.
- Troubleshooting & providing colleagues with IT support.
- Teaching of National Diploma students of Abuja Pension School, a subsidiary of Retirement Benefits Advisory.
- Active involvement in the firm's social media content strategy.

THE NIGERIAN HAIKU COMMUNITY (Lagos, Nigeria)

MAY 2020 - DEC 2020

Social Media & Community Manager

- Day to day creation and curation of social media content.
- Identification and expansion of target audience which has helped to boost the brand in terms of followership.
- Drafting, sending and responding to emails for members of the community.

SAOFANT PROJECTS LIMITED (Abuja, Nigeria)

MARCH 2019 - OCTOBER 2019

Personal Assistant to the MD/CEO

- Answering telephone and providing callers with valuable information, taking messages and transferring calls to the appropriate channel.
- Charged with the responsibility of drafting internal correspondences and circulating same within and outside the organization.
- Reminding the MD and other executives within the firm of important tasks and deadlines daily.
- Typing, compiling and preparing reports, and presentations.

ALARAN GROUP OF SCHOOLS (Bode Sa'adu, Kwara)

APRIL 2018 - MARCH 2019

English Language & Literature-in-English Teacher (National Youth Service Corps)

- Creation of engaging lesson notes for SS1 SS3 students.
- Teaching and explanation of appropriate topics using an easy to understand approach.

Contact

Address:

Abuja, Nigeria

Phone:

+234-902-772-7023

Email:

Sidiali0203@gmail.com

Hobbies

- Traveling
- Sight-seeing
- Listening to music
- Writing

Application Proficiency

Microsoft Office

Adobe Photoshop

Canva

Adobe Premiere

Pro

Corel Draw

ECOWAS Commission (Abuja, Nigeria)

SEPT 2017 - MARCH 2018

Intern (Conference and Protocol Department)

- Booking and buying of flight tickets for staff and visitors.
- Airport pick-up and dispatch of staff and visitors.
- Booking of hotels, lodging of diplomats and helping with formalties.
- Organizing conferences and events by compiling lists of participants, liasing with participants, issuing invitations and booking events venue with food, beverages and stationery.
- Organizing of sitting arrangements during conferences with the appropriate nameplates for participants and Heads of States.
- Preparation of presentations for conferences and summits using appropriate applications like Powerpoint.

Certifications

HUBSPOT ACADEMY

Social Media Certification (June 2020)

ACCENTURE

Certificate of achievement in Digital Skills: Digital Marketing. Url link: https://www.futurelearn.com/certificates/imvvmn4 (November 2019)

ACCENTURE

Certificate of achievement in Digital Skills: Social Media. Url link: https://www.futurelearn.com/certificates/sri3cse (October 2019)

Education

NASARAWA STATE UNIVERSITY, KEFFI

Bsc (Hons), Mass Communication, 2013 - 2017

LILY FIELDS COMPREHENSIVE COLLEGE, LAGOS

West African Senior Secondary School Certificate (WASSCE) 2010 - 2011

Referees

- Mrs. Bukola Seun-Babalola, ECOWAS Commission, Abuja. 08067775650
- Mr. Wasiu Salami
 Television Continental, Lagos.
 07063822184

